<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<?xml-model href="../grammar/ci-specification.sch" type="application/xml" schematypens="http://purl.oclc.org/dsdl/schematron"?>
<component-inventory-specification xmlns="https://eriksiegel.nl/ns/component-inventory" xmlns:sml="http://www.eriksiegel.nl/ns/sml"
  xmlns:xsi="http://www.w3.org/2001/XMLSchema-instance"
  xsi:schemaLocation="https://eriksiegel.nl/ns/component-inventory ../grammar/ci-specification.xsd">

  <!-- - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - -->

  <properties>

    <!-- General: -->
    <property id="max-current" name="Maximum current" value-pattern="^-?[0-9]+$" suffix="mA"/>

    <!-- For transistors: -->
    <property id="collector-to-base" name="Collector to base voltage" suffix="V" value-pattern="^-?[0-9]+$"/>
    <property id="collector-to-emitter" name="Collector to emitter voltage" suffix="V" value-pattern="^-?[0-9]+$"/>
    <property id="emitter-to-base" name="Emitter to base voltage" suffix="V" value-pattern="^-?[0-9]+$"/>
    <property id="collector-current" name="Collector current" suffix="mA" value-pattern="^-?[0-9]+$"/>
    <property id="gain" name="Gain" value-pattern="^[0-9]+$"/>

  </properties>

  <!-- - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - -->

  <categories>

    <!-- Simple components: -->
    <category id="comp" name="Simple components">
      <description>
        <p>Straight and simple components, like transistors, MOS-FETs etc.</p>
      </description>
    </category>

    <category id="transistor" name="Transistors"
      optional-property-idrefs="collector-to-base collector-to-emitter emitter-to-base collector-current gain">
      <categories>
        <category id="npn" name="Transistors - NPN">
          <description>
            <sml:fragment>
              <sml:image href="images/NPN.png" scale="10%"/>
            </sml:fragment>
          </description>
        </category>
        <category id="pnp" name="Transistors - PNP">
          <description>
            <sml:fragment>
              <sml:image href="images/PNP.png" scale="10%"/>
            </sml:fragment>
          </description>
        </category>
        <category id="power" name="Transistors - Power"/>
        <category id="dual" name="Transistors - Dual" summary="Two transistors in one package"/>
        <category id="darlington" name="Transistors - Darlington">
          <description>
            <p>A Darlington transistor—also known as a Darlington pair—is an electronic device that combines two bipolar junction transistors so that
              the current amplified by the first is further amplified by the second, resulting in an exceptionally high overall current gain and
              allowing a very small input current to control a much larger output current. In this configuration, the emitter of the first transistor
              feeds the base of the second, and both collectors are typically tied together, making the pair behave like a single transistor with one
              base, one collector, and one emitter. </p>
          </description>
        </category>
        <category id="special" summary="Transistors - Special"/>
      </categories>
    </category>

    <category id="mos-fet" name="MOS-FETs">
      <description>
        <p>A MOS-FET (Metal-Oxide-Semiconductor Field-Effect Transistor) is a voltage-controlled semiconductor device that uses an insulated gate to
          regulate how much current flows between its source and drain terminals, allowing it to function efficiently as a switch or amplifier. Its
          gate is separated from the conducting channel by a thin oxide layer, so applying a voltage creates an electric field that either enables or
          blocks current flow, depending on the MOS-FET type (enhancement or depletion, and N-channel or P-channel). Because it requires almost no
          input current, switches quickly, and consumes very little power, the MOS-FET is the most widely used transistor in modern digital and power
          electronics, forming the foundation of microprocessors, memory chips, and many switching circuits.</p>
      </description>
      <categories>
        <category id="power" name="MOS-FETs - Power">
          <description>
            <p>A MOS-FET (Metal-Oxide-Semiconductor Field-Effect Transistor) is a voltage-controlled semiconductor device that uses an insulated gate
              to regulate how much current flows between its source and drain terminals, allowing it to function efficiently as a switch or amplifier.
              Its gate is separated from the conducting channel by a thin oxide layer, so applying a voltage creates an electric field that either
              enables or blocks current flow, depending on the MOS-FET type (enhancement or depletion, and N-channel or P-channel). Because it
              requires almost no input current, switches quickly, and consumes very little power, the MOS-FET is the most widely used transistor in
              modern digital and power electronics, forming the foundation of microprocessors, memory chips, and many switching circuits.</p>
          </description>
        </category>
      </categories>
    </category>

    <category id="thyristor" name="Thyristors">
      <description>
        <p>A thyristor is a four-layer semiconductor device that acts as a solid-state switch, designed to handle high voltages and large currents in
          power-control applications. It remains in a non-conductive “off” state until a small trigger current is applied to its gate, at which point
          it rapidly switches to a conductive “on” state and continues conducting as long as current flows above a certain holding threshold. This
          latching behavior makes thyristors ideal for controlling AC power, such as in motor drives, light dimmers, and controlled rectifiers, where
          precise timing of switching is essential. Their robustness, efficiency, and ability to manage significant electrical loads have made them
          foundational components in power electronics.</p>
      </description>
    </category>
    <category id="triac" name="Triacs">
      <description>
        <p>A triac is a bidirectional, three-terminal semiconductor device used for controlling AC power, capable of switching current on both halves
          of an AC waveform. Functionally similar to two thyristors connected in opposite directions, it can be triggered into conduction by a small
          gate current regardless of the polarity of the voltage across it. Once turned on, it remains conducting until the current naturally drops
          below its holding level, making it ideal for applications like lamp dimmers, motor-speed controllers, and heater regulation. Its ability to
          modulate power smoothly and efficiently in AC circuits has made the triac a staple component in many household and industrial control
          systems.</p>
      </description>
    </category>


    <!-- Digital components: -->
    <category id="I2C" name="I2C related products">
      <description>
        <p>I²C (Inter-Integrated Circuit) is a simple, low-speed, two-wire communication protocol designed for short-distance data exchange between
          chips on the same circuit board. It uses just two shared lines—SDA for data and SCL for the clock—to let multiple “slave” devices
          communicate with one “master” controller without needing separate wiring for each connection. Each device has a unique address, and the
          master controls when data is sent, making the bus efficient and easy to scale. Because it’s lightweight, flexible, and inexpensive to
          implement, I²C is widely used in embedded systems to connect sensors, displays, memory chips, and other peripherals.</p>
      </description>
    </category>
    <category id="memory" name="Computer memory"/>
    <category id="timer" name="Timer/timing related"/>
    <category id="74HC">
      <description>
        <p>The 74HC (High-Speed CMOS) IC series is a family of logic chips known for combining the low-power characteristics of CMOS technology with
          the speed of traditional TTL logic. These devices operate over a wide supply-voltage range—typically 2 V to 6 V—while offering fast
          switching times, high noise immunity, and very low power consumption compared to older logic families. They are pin- and function-compatible
          with the classic 74LS series, making them easy drop-in replacements in many designs, but with significantly improved performance. Because of
          their versatility, speed, and efficiency, 74HC chips are widely used in modern digital electronics for tasks like buffering, decoding,
          timing, and general logic control.</p>
      </description>
    </category>
    <category id="SN74">
      <description>
        <p>The SN74 series is a broad family of Texas Instruments logic ICs built on modern CMOS technology, offering fast switching speeds, low power
          consumption, and wide operating voltage ranges that make them suitable for both classic digital logic tasks and contemporary embedded
          designs. These devices maintain functional compatibility with earlier 7400-series logic while improving electrical performance, noise
          immunity, and efficiency. The SN74 lineup includes gates, flip-flops, counters, buffers, translators, and many other building-block
          functions, giving designers a flexible toolkit for constructing reliable digital systems across industrial, consumer, and automotive
          applications.</p>
      </description>
    </category>
    <category id="cmos" name="CMOS">
      <description>
        <p>CMOS (Complementary Metal-Oxide-Semiconductor) ICs are defined by their extremely low power consumption, high noise immunity, and wide
          operating-voltage range, all made possible by using complementary pairs of p-channel and n-channel MOSFETs that draw almost no current
          except when switching. This design gives CMOS logic excellent energy efficiency, making it ideal for battery-powered and portable devices,
          while also enabling high-density integration for complex digital circuits. CMOS ICs typically offer slower edge speeds than some
          high-performance logic families but compensate with minimal heat generation, strong reliability, and broad applicability across
          microprocessors, memory chips, sensors, and general-purpose logic functions.</p>
      </description>
    </category>
    <category id="HEF4000">
      <description>
        <p>The HEF series is a family of CMOS logic ICs known for their extremely low power consumption, wide operating-voltage range (typically 3 V
          to 15 V), and high noise immunity, making them well-suited for both battery-powered and industrial applications. These devices follow the
          classic 4000-series CMOS logic functions but offer improved speed and robustness, while maintaining compatibility with a broad variety of
          digital systems. Because they draw very little current and tolerate higher supply voltages than many other logic families, HEF chips are
          often used in analog-digital interfacing, timing circuits, and general-purpose logic where reliability and efficiency are key.</p>
      </description>
    </category>
    <category id="microcontroller" name="Micro-controllers"/>

    <category id="logic" name="Logic ICs">
      <categories>
        <category id="schmitt-trigger" name="Schmitt triggers">
          <description>
            <p>A Schmitt trigger is a type of comparator circuit with built-in hysteresis, meaning it uses two different threshold voltages to
              determine when its output switches between high and low states. This dual-threshold behavior prevents rapid, noisy, or slowly changing
              input signals from causing erratic output transitions, making the circuit excellent for cleaning up noisy waveforms, debouncing
              mechanical switches, and converting analog signals into crisp digital pulses. By ensuring that the input must cross a higher threshold
              to switch one way and a lower threshold to switch back, a Schmitt trigger provides stable, predictable switching even in electrically
              noisy environments.</p>
          </description>
        </category>
        <category id="nand" name="NAND gates"/>
        <category id="and" name="AND gates"/>
        <category id="nor" name="NOR gates"/>
        <category id="or" name="OR gates"/>
        <category id="xor" name="XOR gates"/>
        <category id="inverter" name="Inverters"/>
        <category id="non-inverter" name="Non-inverter drivers"/>
        <category id="comparator" name="Logic comparators"/>
        <category id="computation" name="Digital computation"/>
        <category id="multiplexer" name="Multiplexers"/>
        <category id="demultiplexer" name="Demultiplexers"/>
        <category id="decoder" name="Decoders"/>
        <category id="counter" name="Counters">
          <categories>
            <category id="johnson-decade">
              <description>
                <p>A Johnson decade counter is a type of shift-register-based counter that cycles through ten unique states by feeding the inverted
                  output of the last flip-flop back into the first. As the clock advances, a single stream of ones and zeros “walks” through the
                  register in a predictable pattern, producing a sequence that is easy to decode and inherently glitch-resistant. Because it generates
                  ten distinct, evenly spaced states with minimal decoding logic, a Johnson decade counter is often used in timing circuits, LED
                  chasers, frequency dividers, and other applications where a clean, repeatable 10-step sequence is needed.</p>
              </description>
            </category>
            <category id="johnson">
              <description>
                <p>A Johnson counter is a type of shift-register-based sequential circuit that generates a repeating sequence of states by feeding the
                  inverted output of the last flip-flop back into the first. As the clock advances, a pattern of ones and zeros circulates through the
                  register in a predictable “walking” sequence that is twice the length of the number of stages. This produces a set of easily
                  decoded, non-overlapping states with minimal logic, making Johnson counters useful in timing generators, LED chasers, frequency
                  division, and other applications where a clean, cyclic sequence of digital states is needed.</p>
              </description>
            </category>
          </categories>
        </category>
        <category id="shift-register" name="Shift registers"/>
        <category id="transceiver" name="Transceivers">
          <description>
            <p>A digital transceiver is an integrated communication device that both transmits and receives digital signals, enabling reliable two-way
              data exchange between electronic systems. Unlike analog transceivers, it processes information as discrete binary values, which improves
              noise immunity, supports error detection and correction, and allows for higher-speed, protocol-driven communication. Digital
              transceivers are used in everything from microcontroller serial interfaces and wireless modules to high-speed networking equipment,
              where they serve as the essential bridge between digital logic and the physical communication medium.</p>
          </description>
        </category>
        <category id="addressable-latch">
          <description>
            <p>An addressable latch is a digital storage element that allows one of several latch cells to be individually selected and updated using
              an address input, while all others remain unchanged. It typically combines a bank of simple latches with a decoder so that only the
              latch corresponding to the active address line responds to the data and enable signals. This structure makes it efficient for building
              small register files, configuration registers, or memory-mapped control blocks, because a single shared data path can write to many
              storage locations without needing separate control lines for each one.</p>
          </description>
        </category>
        <category id="d-type-latch" name="D-type latches">
          <description>
            <p>A D-type latch is a level-sensitive storage element that captures the value on its data input D whenever its enable signal is active,
              and holds that value steady when the enable signal is inactive. While the latch is “open,” the output follows the input continuously;
              once the enable signal goes low, the latch “closes” and preserves the last input value, effectively storing a single bit until it is
              enabled again. This makes D-type latches useful for controlled data flow, temporary storage, and building larger sequential circuits
              where timing and transparency behavior matter.</p>
          </description>
        </category>
        <category id="switch" name="Switches">
          <description>
            <p>A digital switch is an integrated circuit that uses MOSFET-based analog switches to route or isolate signals under digital control.
              Each switch behaves like a voltage-controlled resistor: when its control input is activated, the internal MOSFET conducts and allows an
              analog or digital signal to pass with low resistance; when deactivated, it presents a very high resistance, effectively disconnecting
              the path. Devices like the 74HC4316 offer multiple independently controlled bilateral switches, making them useful for signal
              multiplexing, audio routing, sensor selection, and other applications where flexible, low-distortion switching is needed without
              mechanical relays.</p>
          </description>
        </category>

        <category id="flip-flop" name="Flip-flops">
          <description>
            <p>A flip-flop is a fundamental digital memory element that stores a single bit of information by maintaining one of two stable output
              states until an input signal causes it to change. Unlike simple logic gates, a flip-flop is sequential, meaning its output depends not
              only on current inputs but also on its previous state, allowing it to act as a tiny, clocked memory cell. By responding predictably to
              control signals—such as clock pulses, set/reset inputs, or data lines—flip-flops form the backbone of registers, counters, and virtually
              all synchronous digital systems where reliable state retention and timing are essential.</p>
          </description>
          <categories>
            <category id="d-type" name="D-type flip-flops">
              <description>
                <p>A D-type flip-flop is a digital storage element that captures the value present on its data input (D) at the moment of a triggering
                  clock edge and then holds that value stable at its output (Q) until the next clock event. Internally, it uses gating logic to ensure
                  that only the value at the precise clock transition—typically the rising or falling edge—is latched, making it ideal for building
                  synchronous circuits where timing and state progression must be tightly controlled. Because it cleanly separates input sampling from
                  output holding, the D-flip-flop is the fundamental building block for registers, counters, finite-state machines, and virtually all
                  modern sequential logic.</p>
              </description>
            </category>
            <category id="jk" name="JK flip-flops">
              <description>
                <p>A JK flip-flop is a versatile, edge-triggered storage element that extends the behavior of an SR flip-flop while eliminating its
                  invalid input state. It has two inputs—J and K—and on each triggering clock edge it updates its output based on their combination:
                  J=1 and K=0 sets the output, J=0 and K=1 resets it, J=0 and K=0 holds the current state, and J=1 and K=1 toggles the output. This
                  predictable, flexible behavior makes the JK flip-flop useful in counters, frequency dividers, and general sequential logic where
                  controlled state transitions are needed.</p>
              </description>
            </category>
          </categories>

        </category>
      </categories>

    </category>

    <category id="pll" name="Phase-locked loops">
      <description>
        <p>A phase-locked loop (PLL) is a feedback control system that synchronizes the phase and frequency of an output oscillator with a reference
          signal, effectively “locking” the two together. It continuously compares the phase of the reference with that of a voltage-controlled
          oscillator (VCO), generating an error signal that adjusts the VCO until both signals match in phase and frequency. Once locked, the PLL can
          track small variations, filter noise, multiply frequencies, or generate highly stable clock signals, making it indispensable in
          communication systems, microprocessors, radio receivers, and any application requiring precise timing and frequency control. </p>
      </description>
    </category>

    <!-- Various: -->
    <category id="analogue-switch" name="Analogue switches"/>
    <category id="converter" name="Converters"/>
    <category id="filter" name="Filters"/>
    <category id="driver" name="Drivers"/>
    <category id="motor-driver" name="Motor drivers"/>
    <category id="analog-computation" name="Analogue computation"/>
    <category id="opamp" name="Operational amplifiers">
      <description>
        <p>An operational amplifier, or op-amp, is a high-gain differential amplifier designed to compare two input voltages and produce an output
          that reflects their difference, making it one of the most versatile building blocks in analog electronics. With extremely high input
          impedance, very low output impedance, and a large open-loop gain, an op-amp can be configured using external resistors and components to
          perform a wide range of functions such as amplification, filtering, summing, integration, differentiation, and signal conditioning. Because
          of this flexibility and its predictable linear behavior when used with feedback, the op-amp is foundational in audio circuits, sensors,
          control systems, and countless analog signal-processing applications.</p>
      </description>
    </category>
    <category id="optocoupler" name="Optocouplers">
      <description>
        <p>An optocoupler, also known as an optoisolator, is a device that transfers electrical signals between two isolated circuits using light,
          providing a safe and reliable way to prevent high voltages or electrical noise from passing between them. It typically contains an LED on
          the input side and a light-sensitive component—such as a phototransistor, photodiode, or phototriac—on the output side, all sealed within a
          single package. When the LED turns on, it emits light that activates the output device, allowing the signal to cross the isolation barrier
          without any direct electrical connection. This makes optocouplers essential in protecting microcontrollers, communication interfaces, and
          low-voltage electronics from surges, spikes, and ground-loop issues in power supplies, industrial controls, and switching circuits.</p>
      </description>
    </category>
    <category id="dac" name="Digital-analog converter">
      <description>
        <p> A DAC, or Digital-to-Analog Converter, is an electronic device that transforms digital data—typically a series of binary numbers—into a
          corresponding analog voltage or current, allowing digital systems to interface with the analog world. By converting discrete digital values
          into smooth, continuous signals, DACs enable microcontrollers, computers, and digital audio systems to drive speakers, control motors,
          generate waveforms, and produce precise analog outputs. Their performance is defined by factors like resolution, sampling rate, linearity,
          and noise, all of which determine how accurately the analog output represents the original digital information. </p>
      </description>
    </category>
    <category id="rectifier" name="Rectifiers">
      <description>
        <p>A rectifier is an electronic circuit or device that converts alternating current (AC) into direct current (DC), making it essential for
          powering most electronic equipment that requires a steady, one-directional flow of electricity. It works by using diodes—or controlled
          devices like thyristors—to allow current to pass only during specific portions of the AC cycle, effectively blocking the reverse direction.
          Rectifiers come in several forms, such as half-wave, full-wave, and bridge configurations, each offering different levels of efficiency and
          smoothness in the resulting DC output. They are widely used in power supplies, battery chargers, and any system that needs to transform AC
          mains power into usable DC energy.</p>
      </description>
    </category>
    <category id="display" name="Display related components"/>
    <category id="radio" summary="Radio related components"/>
    <category id="thermal" name="Thermal switches"/>
    <category id="communication" name="Communication related ICs"/>
    <category id="oscillator" name="Oscillators"/>
    <category id="audio" name="Audio related components"/>
    <category id="movement" name="Movement related components"/>
    <category id="modulator" summary="Modulators"/>
    <category id="demodulator" summary="Demodulators"/>
    <category id="gyrator" summary="Gyrators">
      <description>
        <p>A gyrator is an active circuit element that mimics the behavior of an inductor by using amplifiers and capacitors to create an impedance
          that looks inductive at its terminals. Because real inductors can be bulky, expensive, or impractical at low frequencies, a gyrator provides
          a compact, tunable alternative that preserves the same reactive characteristics—such as phase shift and energy storage—without requiring a
          physical coil. This makes gyrators especially useful in analog signal processing, where they enable filters, equalizers, and resonant
          circuits to be built using only resistors, capacitors, and active devices.</p>
      </description>
    </category>
    <category id="voltage-comparator" name="Voltage comparators">
      <description>
        <p>A voltage comparator is an electronic circuit designed to compare two input voltages and switch its output to a defined high or low state
          depending on which input is greater. Unlike an op-amp, which is optimized for linear amplification, a comparator is built for fast, clean
          transitions and typically operates in saturation, making it ideal for turning analog signals into digital logic levels. When the
          non-inverting input rises above the inverting input, the output snaps to its high state; when it falls below, the output switches low. This
          sharp switching behavior makes comparators essential in applications like threshold detection, zero-crossing detection, waveform shaping,
          and many types of control and timing circuits.</p>
      </description>
    </category>
    <category id="voltage-regulator" name="Voltage regulators">
      <description>
        <p>A voltage regulator is an electronic device or circuit that maintains a stable, constant output voltage despite changes in input voltage,
          load current, or other external conditions, ensuring that sensitive electronics receive clean and reliable power. It works by continuously
          monitoring its output and adjusting its internal resistance or switching behavior to compensate for fluctuations, preventing overvoltage or
          undervoltage conditions. Regulators come in linear and switching types: linear regulators provide low noise and simplicity, while switching
          regulators offer higher efficiency and can handle larger voltage differences. They are essential in power supplies for everything from
          microcontrollers to industrial equipment, where consistent voltage is critical for proper operation.</p>
      </description>
    </category>
    <category id="voltage-translator" name="Voltage translators"/>

    <category id="diode" name="Diodes" optional-property-idrefs="max-current"/>

    <!-- For everything we can't identify or don't know how to categorize: -->
    <category id="unknown" summary="Unknown components"/>

  </categories>

  <!-- - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - -->

  <price-ranges>
    <price-range id="very-cheap" max-inclusive="0.50" min-inclusive="0.00" name="Very cheap (less than €0.50)"/>
    <price-range id="cheap" max-inclusive="2.00" min-inclusive="0.51" name="Cheap (between €0.50 and €2)"/>
    <price-range id="expensive" max-inclusive="10.00" min-inclusive="2.01" name="Expensive (between €2 and €10)"/>
    <price-range id="very-expensive" max-inclusive="1000.00" min-inclusive="10.01" name="Very expensive (over €10)."/>
  </price-ranges>

  <!-- - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - -->

  <packages href-default-base-directory="packaging">
    <package id="DIP4" summary="4-pin dual inline package"/>
    <package id="DIP6" summary="6-pin dual inline package"/>
    <package id="DIP8" summary="8-pin dual inline package"/>
    <package id="DIP14" summary="14-pin dual inline package"/>
    <package id="DIP16" summary="16-pin dual inline package"/>
    <package id="DIP18" summary="18-pin dual inline package"/>
    <package id="DIP20" summary="20-pin dual inline package"/>
    <package id="DIP24" summary="24-pin dual inline package"/>
    <package id="DIP28" summary="28-pin dual inline package"/>
    <package id="DIP40" summary="40-pin dual inline package"/>

    <package id="TO3"/>
    <package id="TO8"/>
    <package id="TO18"/>
    <package id="TO39"/>
    <package id="TO71"/>
    <package id="TO72"/>
    <package id="TO92"/>
    <package id="TO126"/>
    <package id="TO220"/>
    <package id="TO225"/>
    <package id="TO247"/>
    <package id="TO998"/>
    <package id="TO3PN"/>

    <package id="SMD" name="SMD package">
      <description>
        <p>SMD, or Surface-Mount Device, refers to electronic components designed to be mounted directly onto the surface of a printed circuit board
          rather than inserted through holes, allowing for much smaller, lighter, and more densely packed circuits. These components typically have
          flat leads or contact pads instead of long wire pins, enabling automated placement and soldering processes that improve manufacturing speed,
          reliability, and consistency. Because SMD parts support high-density layouts and reduced parasitic effects, they’re widely used in modern
          electronics ranging from smartphones to industrial equipment, where compact size and efficient assembly are essential.</p>
      </description>
    </package>
  </packages>

  <!-- - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - -->

  <locations>
    <location id="box-sub-boxes" name="Component box (with sub-boxes)"/>
    <location id="bag" name="Plastic bag in storage container"/>
    <location id="box-workbench" name="Component box above workbench"/>
  </locations>

  <!-- - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - - -->

  <components>
    <directory href="components"/>
    <directory href="components-opamps"/>
    <directory href="components-simple"/>
    <directory href="components-analog"/>
    <directory href="components-digital"/>
    <directory href="components-other"/>

  </components>

</component-inventory-specification>
